<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ray&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ray&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Lists, Databases and Scoring</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/vulnerability_scoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/vulnerability_scoring/</guid>
      <description>In this post I wanted to go over some of the findings I have found when doing research into how vulnerability scoring works with vulnerability databases.
CVE List The Common Enumeration of Vulnerabilities (CVE) List is a database of reported vulnerabilities maintained by the Mitre Corporation. Vulnerabilities found can be submitted by organizations and even individuals. Each vulnerability is given a CVE-ID number to identify by. This list of CVE-ID&amp;rsquo;s is used by many other databases for application use and scoring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AppSec Open Source I Have Come Across</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/appsec_open_source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/appsec_open_source/</guid>
      <description>Tools Brakeman Scanner:
Able to detect vulnerabilities on the latest Ruby on Rails version. https://brakemanscanner.org OWASP Dependency-Check:
Able to detect vulnerabilities in project&amp;rsquo;s depedencies. https://dependencytrack.org </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The BASpi - A Configurable BACnet Raspberry Pi Hat</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/baspi_installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/baspi_installation/</guid>
      <description>The BASpi is a raspberry pi HAT that can turn your raspbery pi into a configurable BACnet device. BACnet devices are used in commercial HVAC building automation. It is how large commercial buildings are able to trigger during a certain time of day or trigger from another sensor. For example, a BACnet devices can be used for turning down and turning up building air conditioning during certain times of day or year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blog Created with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/blog_site_created/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/blog_site_created/</guid>
      <description>Like everyone else and their dog, I set up this blog website to post about personal projects in technology and other fun topics.
Set up this blog website with Hugo Project and PaperMod Theme:
Docs: Hugo Docs: https://gohugo.io/documentation/ PaperMod Docs: https://github.com/adityatelange/hugo-PaperMod/wiki/Features Deployment: Hugo Local Install: Mac Terminal Installation and Start: Brew Install Hugo git init git submodule add https://github.com/adityatelange/hugo-PaperMod/wiki/Features#profile-mode themes/hugo-PaperMod hugo server -D GitHub Pages Deployment: Hope there are good things to come!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
