<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ray&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ray&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://raymonhardy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Security engineer just trying to keep up with the latest technology and threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Databases</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/vulnerability_databases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/vulnerability_databases/</guid>
      <description>In this post I wanted to go over some of the findings I have found when doing research into how vulnerability scoring works with vulnerability databases.
CVE List The Common Enumeration of Vulnerabilities (CVE) List is a database of reported vulnerabilities maintained by the Mitre Corporation. Vulnerabilities found can be submitted by organizations and even individuals. Each vulnerability is given a CVE-ID number to identify by. This list of CVE-ID&amp;rsquo;s is used by many other databases for application use and scoring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mulesoft Security Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/mulesoft_security_capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/mulesoft_security_capabilities/</guid>
      <description>After working with Mulesoft for a while, I wanted to write this blog post because I didn&amp;rsquo;t see very many resourse that were comprehensive on Mulesoft and it&amp;rsquo;s security capabilities. Many of these findings were by google searching, reviewing Mulesoft documentation and talking with Mulesoft reps for security capabilities. This post is not intented to include all of Mulesoft security capabilities but is just good starter for those looking to use Mulesoft security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baspi Installation</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/baspi_installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/baspi_installation/</guid>
      <description>The BASpi is a raspberry pi HAT that can turn your raspbery pi into a configurable BACnet device. BACnet devices are used in commercial HVAC building automation. It is how large commercial buildings are able to trigger during a certain time of day or trigger from another sensor. For example, a BACnet devices can be used for turning down and turning up building air conditioning during certain times of day or year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blog Created with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/blog_site_created/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/posts/blog_site_created/</guid>
      <description>Like everyone else and their dog, I set up this blog website to post about personal projects in technology and other fun topics.
Set up this blog website with Hugo Project and PaperMod Theme on mac computer:
Doc URLs: Hugo Docs PaperMod Docs Hugo Deployment types Deployment: Hugo Local Install and Server: Mac Terminal: Brew Install Hugo git init git submodule add https://github.com/adityatelange/hugo-PaperMod/wiki/Features#profile-mode themes/hugo-PaperMod hugo server -D Publish Files to Public Folder Go to project in terminal Build the published version by running: hugo GitHub Pages Deployment: Go to Github.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Open Source Projects</title>
      <link>https://raymonhardy.github.io/lists/open-source-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://raymonhardy.github.io/lists/open-source-list/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of some open source projects I thought were fun and interesting. I will continually update this list of projects I find.
Application Security: Brakeman Scanner:
Able to detect vulnerabilities on the latest Ruby on Rails version. OWASP Dependency-Check:
Able to detect vulnerabilities in project&amp;rsquo;s depedencies. Secure Code Game
An application security coding game tuned for developers to correct vulnerabilities found. CodeQL
Open source code scanning tool provided by GitHub.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
